Hello everyone and welcome to this new video. It's a try on haul because I ordered at H&M
and it's sale season. I think, what sale is it? I think it's winter sale.
Everything was discounted up to I think 70% and stuff and everything is fake leather.
I'm going to unpack everything and then I'm going to try it on. Let's go and watch this video.
So I'm done unpacking and I have a huge pile of clothes but I also have a huge pile of
waste and plastic bags. So of course with all the online shopping it's a lot of trash.
I jumped right into the first outfit. It's a long sleeve top and shorts and I paired it with some
sheer tights and open-knee boots and I think it's really a lot of fake leather and leather look but
it looks really cool. I'm surprised that I like it that much. I especially like the shorts
because the pockets are cool and I like to put my hands in pockets.
It was a bit of a struggle to get into the top because there's a really small zipper in the neck
and still it was really tight but now it fits rather good so I'm happy with both
of them I think this was like super cheap and even with the discount it was
like five euro like what yeah I think this is a really cool fall or winter
outfit especially with over knee boots cool I'm going to search for the next
outfit. Kind of feel like, I don't know, a secretary with this skirt and this blouse.
I like the sleeves, puffy sleeves, but I'm not sure about, I don't know, the waist here.
I feel that it's a loose fit, but maybe I'm just not used to it, but I can also try and
put it in the skirt.
The skirt is pretty cool by the way, although I'm not used to the length.
Well, I think that's better.
Because it accentuates the figure and the waist.
And with a high waist skirt it works better this way.
To go with the gold theme of the shoes
And to, I don't know, make it a bit more adventurous, I'm going to put on my trusty metal belt.
That's cool!
That's a look right here!
Way better than the first version with the loose fit top.
Still not used to the length of the skirt but somehow this is really cool.
I like this outfit as a whole with the shoes and belt and maybe now some golden bracelets
or whatever but damn that's nice.
I'm not sure.
I mean this blouse is giving off serious like 80s vibes or something with the bright broad shoulders here.
Although I really like that it's really snarkier at the waist.
So it feels like this blouse is schizophrenic.
Somehow tight, white, I don't know.
I paired it with some faux leather leggings I bought ages ago at H&M in Australia.
And I put on my Fernando Berlin crotch high leather boots, so everything leather and faux leather again.
I mean, it's okay with the blouse. It's not terrible. Kind of feeling like it's okay.
Not sure I will wear it out ever, because it's not really my style. It's super fun that there's
apparently a lot of fake leather stuff going on at H&M. I remember when I was a
teenager I bought all my stuff there like all the plain cotton outfits you
normally wear every day and in the past such or like 10 years ago you did not
find such outfits at H&M and it's always better to shop at the autumn winter
month because in summer it's just too bright and frilly and flowery. So let's
go to the next outfit. Short little black dress, worn for every occasion maybe not
every because back is rather daring. So it's only supposed to close it.
And yeah, otherwise I think it's a bit lame. I don't know. I'm not a fan of these puffy sleeves somehow. I think other ones are better. I don't know. Well yeah, it's rather plain from the front.
and it's okay but it's not my favorite here I don't know although the shoes and
ties work good with it but not the best one although it's okay it fits obviously
now on to the last outfit okay so these pants are basically a size too small
They're too short, they're too tight. I managed to squeeze into them.
But yeah I can't sit down now because they're too tight. I paired it with this crop top.
Although the pants are that high that there is not really the crop of the top showing.
Yeah not really a fan of this combination I don't know. I have to say that this top
does really feel kind of cheap and makes plastic noises so it's not really a good
fake leather. Or a really bad one. Also I don't like this puffy sleeves. I don't
know why. I think the other ones are way better from this top here. Yeah and even
the ones from the dress have been better. So yeah I think the dress overall was
better than this one. So I think this is like my least favorite outfit from this haul. I think I
have to resell this stuff to someone with the right size. All right I hope you had a lot of fun
with all this faux leather. A lot of fake leather. Yeah I'm done here. I have to change into something
not fake litter like for now okay have a nice evening please subscribe to my channel
and I don't know see you around at the next video